So you want an alliance against
the Mongols in exchange for Halime?
You forced me into this, Osman Bey.
You caused this trouble by
killing Esenbike and her son.
Whoever put this blame on us, I will find them.
But their fate will be nothing but death.
Didn't you want to come together with my Poena?
Not Poena, Halime!
Even if you made her forget
her name, she is still my Halime.
Yes, that's true.
I made her forget the tent life.
I raised her like a noble
girl in the palaces of Rome.
You took my daughter from my arms by force.
And now you come and set
conditions to give her back to me?
This is your only chance to find her.
Either you agree with me, Osman Bey...
...or I'll send Poena to Constantinople
to protect her from Olcaytu.
Aunt!
Your mouth's bleeding!
I'm dying. Poena.
Is she really dying?
The little gazelle kept running.
She went deep into the forest.
Then...
...the Jackal.
The jackal came to the gazelle...
...did not make a noise, and said...
..."Little gazelle...
Don't wander around here like this."
Father..
Mother...
No.
I cannot stay here any longer.
Open the door!
Mistress Sofia ordered you not to
leave the room until she returns.
Damn it!
Look Sofia.
Look right into our eyes.
You took our child from us once.
But it won't happen again.
I swear, we will not let
you leave this tribe alive.
Then...
...Poena will be breathing far away from you.
Look at me.
Don't you have even a
little bit of honor or grace?
For me, honor...
...means protecting my
land from Turks and Mongols.
And don't forget, you are the invaders.
Your rule only brings cruelty to the people.
The real matter is to help the oppressed.
Then you won't turn your
back on the people of Bursa.
Because of you...
...the Mongols will kill them.
Until we fight against each other again...
...we will get over...
...this trouble together.
Think and decide.
But for the fate of the borders and Poena...
...this is the last chance.
Gather the council now!
Are we going to let her go, my Bey?
Mother, this devil is leaving.
Are we going to let her go?
If we don't make an alliance,
we can't see your sister again.
But we cannot make an alliance with this demon.
She didn't just take my
memories, but my hair too.
I don't look like you, mother.
You are merciful. You are good.
And I...
I betrayed you.
How can I come to you?
How can I look into those beautiful
eyes that shed tears for me?
I can't come, mother.
I can't look at your face.
Forgive me, mother.
Forgive me, father..
In the council of Beys, we set our target.
We lost countless martyrs for this cause.
But snake Sofia's offer of peace
requires us not to claw the headquarters.
Right, my Bey?
They're threatening me...
...with my precious daughter.
But no.
I will neither leave my martyrs to heathens...
...or stop before capturing
these lands watered...
...with their blood.
When you give the order.
...we will never avoid...
...taking revenge and capturing that heathen
nest which opens a door into Bursa, my Bey.
What about my sister Halime, my Bey?
When we capture the headquarters.
...Sofia will take her away.
This is such a challenge...
Whichever direction we
go, it will hurt out hearts.
You think it doesn't hurt our hearts...
...while we decide to fight?
We won't leave my sister to heathens.
But we won't give up either...
...by trusting demon Sofia's words.
Those who shout the
requirements of being a Bey...
...also know that a Bey should suspect first.
No, not at all.
I can say no words before great Orhan Bey.
Alaaddin.
When did you become so shortsighted?
You're even afraid of the word fight.
You say drawing back to
survive is a shortsighted action.
What about sending your soldiers
to death on purpose for ambition?
You call me shortsighted, but...
...you are improvident.
You think desire to fight is ambition...
..and not giving up is a mistake, huh?
Alaaddin.
I used to see you as a high
mountain that I could lean on.
What a shame, you turned out to be nothing!
-Orhan Bey!
-Enough!
How impudent you two are!
How impertinent you are before me!
What are you doing? Look at me!
Look at me!
Didn't I tell you boys...
...whoever causes unrest has no place beside me?
Answer me!
So let me, my Bey.
Although it breaks my heart apart,
...let me be the one to separate his way.
So our tribe will have peace...
...and the state will have no unrest.
Let me..
Let me be the one to miss his family.
So the one who says he is
always right will be the Bey.
So he can have both the feast...
..and the hunt!
My Bey.
I don't want to serve my state with my sword...
...but with my wisdom in the frontiers.
If I have your approval.
Get out of my sight.
Get out of my sight!
Whoever wants to leave...
...must go now!
Come on!
With the rest, we will draw our route.
Gonca.
Make your preparations. We're leaving the tribe.
What are you talking about?
What? Where are you going?
Mother, I can't stay here any longer.
We're going to the dervish
lodge to be with my grandfather.
Why?
Mother, if I stay here,
...there will be unrest.
As long as I'm here, there
will be no peace in this tribe.
So I will retreat.
And nobody else will be hurt.
Alaaddin, my son... What does your father say?
He won't let you go.
You can't go.
My father let me, mother.
What?
And he made his decision.
He won't have a deal with Sofia.
He'll raid the headquarters
and take our martyrs.
He won't have a deal with Sofia?
We won't be able to see Halime then.
Sofia.
She wants an alliance against Mongolians.
We'll see if her intention is good or not.
If she still has the same intention after we
captured the headquarters of Derince tomorrow,
..then..
...we will have a temporary
alliance against Mongolians.
If Sofia changes her mind
about the alliance after this
...you may never be able to see your daughter.
Hatun.
Finish your preparations quickly.
We're leaving tomorrow in the morning.
Mother.
What about my sister?
We will never be able to find her.
Bring the horse!
Osman, what are you doing?
Are you sending my son away
and leaving my daughter to her fate?
Osman!
Osman Bey!
Bring my horse!
What are you doing, Osman?
We need to talk.
Come on!
Our people are on the way, Koca Bey.
May Allah be pleased with Osman Bey.
He gave us a homeland and protected us.
And he demanded nothing in return.
Osman Bey is not only a Bey.
He's also the inheritor of
the Turkish state's mind.
He knows traditions and morals.
So his door is open to everyone.
As long as the target is the same.
You're right, Koca Bey.
When our people arrive safely,
we will join Osman Bey's path.
With great pleasure.
Those people coming are Koca
Bey's and Hasan Bey's people.
Osman gave them a land to settle in.
Before Osman shapes in flesh and bones.
I'll cut his flesh and bones into pieces!
The news about the raid will drive Osman mad.
Let him be mad.
I'll get him enslaved by his anger, Hristo.
Kill them.
Kill them all
Osman!
Osman.
How could you let Alaaddin leave?
How could you approve that?
I didn't approve anything.
He said he would leave.
And I let him.
You told him to go?
Bala.
He said he would leave.
He showed weakness.
He's afraid of a power struggle, Osman.
Who would have a power struggle?
They are young.
They made a mistake.
But this can't be punishment.
I'm offering them a glorious state dream.
It's such a dream...
...that there is no place for mistakes.
This path...
...can't be completed with half-hearted ones.
You don't know.
He's not half-hearted.
Leaving in silence shows the wound in his heart.
I'm not only a father.
I'm the head of the state.
I don't care about a son's sorrow...
...but the burden on my nation.
Does the burden of the state
overweights the burden of your son?
You didn't hear his silence.
Because your heart was broken too.
So you kept silent because you were hurt.
Thinking that your son disappointed you.
But your silence made us lose a son.
I'm out of words now.
But I have words to say.
Although he's our son,
...this tribe, this nation, this state...
...can never tolerate weakness.
Fine.
Alaaddin said he'd go and you told him to go.
What about Halime? Our daughter?
Why sacrifice her?
You gave up on your son.
I'm asking you this as a
mother who lost her child.
Are you going to turning your back on her too?
How can you leave our daughter, Osman Bey?
What if we take the headquarters and
our martyrs but lose Halime for ever?
You think it was easy to make this decision?
I prayed before sleeping every night.
I remembered my daughter.
But when I woke up...
...I woke up with the burden of my nation.
I'm not a mother to only the state
but also my children, Osman Bey.
You didn't sacrifice only Alaaddin and Halime...
...but also me today.
I accepted walking beside you.
But you left me behind.
As you carried the state's
burden, you ignored your children.
Today,
...you broke my heart into
pieces, Osman the Brunette.
This is a state matter.
At times..
...your heart should be broken into pieces.
My Bey...
What happened to you, my valiant?
We were raided, my Koca Bey.
They killed our people.
They even killed children and the elderly.
They killed all of them.
Who made this treacherous plan?
The Byzantium infidels, my Bey.
Help please.
If I don't take my revenge for
this, may they not call me Koca Bey!
Come on! To horses!
Bury our Alp.
As you order my Bey.
Come on!
Help us, my Allah...
My Allah..
My dear, my little child...
They killed our people, Koca Bey.
They killed my mother.
What was our fault?
Why did they do this?
We will surely make
those who did this pay for it.
Surely.
My Bey.
The rest of the people are coming from behind.
We came ahead to reach
you first, but we were attacked.
Who attacked you?
Give me his name...
So I can cut his body into pieces!
Cladius!
Take position!
Archers!
...you were the two-horned devil...
...who killed my innocent people, huh?
If I am in a war.
...then I don't..
...care if it's children women, or men.
I kill whoever crosses my path.
Come down here if you have some courage!
Don't hide behind your soldiers!
My sword does not come out of its sheath.
I wonder why...
It says...
...it won't deal with old men like you.
And it is right.
Besides...
...I don't want to kill you.
Why?
Because...
...you will convey my greetings to Osman Bey.
Say whatever you want, infidel!
Stop playing games!
Go and tell Osman what happened here.
Tell him that..
...Cladius will be waiting
for him at the outpost.
If you want to die as well...
...if you are bored of living...
...I will be waiting for you as well.
Hristo
Let's go after them my Bey!
We won't.
Since they dared to come
all the way here and face us...
...they won't retreat without
an ambush behind them.
He called us to the outpost on purpose.
It's clear that the game he set up is big.
Let's go and inform Osman Bey, Koca Bey.
Even if he waits for us...
...we will destroy that outpost, Hasan Bey.
Alaeddin
My Allah, give me patience.
What do you think you are doing, Alaeddin?
How can you leave the tribe?
I don't have to answer you.
Don't stand in my way.
Alaeddin...
You made a mistake at that outpost.
And you are on the wrong way again.
While you still have time..
...give up on this path.
There is no right or wrong now, Orhan Bey.
The things you told me...
...that punch you threw at me...
I don't want to hear a single
word I don't deserve anymore.
One of us needs to leave
for the peace in our tribe.
And since..
...you have this ambition and...
..arrogance..
...I was going to be the one
who would leave anyway.
Why do you keep talking about arrogance?
We will get in a war soon, Alaeddin.
When we needed even a single man...
...what you are doing is leaving us halfway.
It's helping infidels gain a victory.
Don't...
No... How would that even happen Orhan Bey?
As long as you are at the head of the Alps...
...victory will surely belong to the Kayi.
Why would you need me here?
Alaeddin.
Enough!
Don't touch me!
I will destroy all your
limits and your boundaries.
In this tribe..
...the battle will be yours from now on.
Did I think you were different, Alaeddin?
Have my eyes only just opened?
Is my brother really a man to turn his back...
...and leave when his tribe
is in this situation, in a war?
Orhan Bey.
The war cannot be won with just a sword.
I will go and spill ink to prevent
the shedding of martyr's blood.
I will continue my fight on my front.
Don't worry.
Well done, Alaeddin.
Good. Do that.
But you should know, if we are short by
one, the enemy will be one more than us.
Tomorrow, in that battle, every drop of
blood that will be shed from your family...
...will also be your responsibility.
Go now. Leave.
May Allah let you go safely God willing.
May Allah be pleased with you
..brother.
Peace be upon you.
The wolf's cubs have fallen
into conflict with each other.
We too have fought with my brothers.
We too have fought with my uncle.
Tell me, father.
Did we make your heart suffer like this?
No.
We argued
But even though we fought, we never...
...never...
...showed disrespect in your presence.
Never.
We never turned our backs and parted ways.
Now..
My two sons have become enemies.
And my daughter has disappeared
in the hands of the enemy.
My Halime...
My rose-scented child who
carries my mother's name.
Tell me, father
Which is harder, the test with children...
...the test with the state?
We sometimes...
..gave up on our children.
But..
...we never gave up on the state.
And we never will.
Did you achieve your goal, brother?
Has the anger inside you disappear?
Enough, Cerkutay.
Everything is clear. Don't you see?
You have no shame left.
Shame?
Shame for you, honour for me, brother.
Though I appreciate you.
I mean it, you destroyed
the unity in the tribe...
...especially during wartime.
Brother!
Look.
Osman Bey gave up his
own daughter for the state.
What did Alaeddin Bey do?
He can't give up on his honour.
He is defeated by his
mistake and he is now leaving.
Did you leave him any other choice?
You disgraced him before those Alps.
Didn't he deserve it?
Look.
Look around you. Mothers, sisters, and people
are waiting for their martyrs, Cerkutay.
Where are they? At the infidels' borders.
Because of whom? Huh, brother?
Martyrs, huh?
We will take them, brother.
And we won't just take them.
We will turn that land where they
became martyrs into our homeland.
We will, huh?
How will I trust my brother
who I have trusted for years...
...again during the time of war?
Boran.
What do you mean?
Cerkutay.
The one who once runs away from
shahada, always runs away from it!
I will make you swallow that word
now! I will make you swallow it!
-Do it, come on!
-I will! -Do it, brother!
Choose your words wisely!
Cerkutay, am I lying brother? Am I?
Beys, pull yourself together.
Boran Bey, Cerkutay Bey.
You are Beys. The people
are watching us. Don't do this.
Don't, brothers.
Osman Bey shouldn't hear this, it will be bad.
Don't brother, don't.
Come on brother.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
What's the matter? What brought you here?
Our convoy got raided, Osman Bey.
The heathen called Claudius...
...slaughtered our people
ncluding the old and children.
He said he's wait for you with all his strength
in that headquarter which is a snake's nest.
Is that so? Alright then.
I'll give him what he wants.
Let's go.
Ertugrul Bey.
O Ertugrul Bey, the glorious leader of ghazis!
May you rest in heaven.
I have important news
from the tribe, Begum Hatun.
What is so important?
Byzantine witch Sofia wants to work
together with Osman against Mongolians.
And she'll give Osman his daughter as guarantee.
Things will get complicated again.
This fight will be great for us, Ural.
I'll take back my tribe from Osman's
shadow which was stolen from me.
Go back to their tribe and
let me know his every step.
As you order, Begum Hatun.
You took my everything from me.
Yusuf became a martyr...
...hating me because of you.
I'll chase you to the end.
Who are you?
Alps, attack!
I don't know who you serve.
But you made a mistake by confronting me.
Alaeddin Bey can't think
straight due to his anger.
He's making a mistake.
-You have to think...
You think it's Alaeddin's anger?
How could you not see
Alaeddin's patience, Holofira?
If Alaeddin were angry,
he would have hit him back.
Gonca, you're blowing the coals.
If I were the one blowing the coals, we
wouldn't be the ones leaving the tribes.
You can feel at ease now.
Your departure will cause a bigger fire.
If Alaeddin Bey accepts his mistake...
-Holofira.
You still call it a mistake!
Enough!
Neither of you are helping!
My children made a mistake!
Why are you following their paths?
Are you blinded by your anger, Gonca?
No, mother.
No.
How can you raise a child
in this situation, Holofira?
How can you teach your
children brotherhood and family?
I’m sorry, mother.
A mother...
A mother is the hearth.
A hatun is the home.
Everybody breaks things and we repair.
And what are you doing?
You are breaking everything down!
Look at me.
I, Bala Hatun, won't let his happen.
If I see you two in this situation again
..you both will lose my favor!
Now get out!
My Allah, give me strength.
Give me strength, my Allah.
Give me strength.
Poena.
How could you lock me in?
You're imprisoning me now?
I did everything to protect you, Poena.
Don't be angry.
The door is opened now. This is your home.
You protected me?
This lock wasn't for the enemy but me.
Poena.
This lock imprisoned me.
People can't be locked inside their own home.
Where were you?
Where did you go?
Why did you lock me?
I was with your parents.
What are you talking about?
I will help you meet
your family, my little bird.
If they accept my offer, of course.
What do you mean?
What offer?
Who are my family, Sofia?
Sofia?
Yes.
What about aunt?
You expect me to call
you aunt after all your lies?
I haven't forgiven you.
And I never will.
No.
I can't want you to do that.
I want to redeem myself.
Only to make you happy...
..and see my regret, today...
...I visited my biggest enemy.
In the tribe of Osman and Bala.
Osman and Bala?
Did you...
You are the daughter of Osman
and Bala who are my sworn enemy.
You are Halime.
If you are to point your arrow at the eagle.
...you shouldn't aim where it lands...
...but where it's going to fly off.
This is what I expect from all of you!
Get off!
Who are you?
What do you want from me?
Leave her.
Stand up.
I'm the one who is to ask questions, hatun.
Did you have an alliance with Esenbike?
Did you serve her?
-We had the same target.
-You had the same target?
They all died
I'm really wonder how you survived.
I ran away for my life.
Otherwise, I would have
died like Esenbike and Sargun.
Were you there when Osman
killed Esenbike and Sargun?
Motherl
I was there.
Osman killed them both with no mercy.
You say you had an alliance with Esenbike.
Why didn't you stop Osman?
We were outnumbered.
I was on my own.
And I hid out to take revenge from Osman.
Do you have an alliance...
...with the red woman called
Sofia with your thirst for revenge?
It seems you know everything.
Then you must know why we have an alliance.
You can't..
...take revenge from Osman in this condition.
You lost your alps and your tribe got destroyed.
You have only one option.
I will...
...give you a great chance
to take revenge from Osman.
Who are you?
What do you want from me?
I'm the only person...
...can give you your tribe and revenge.
Now tell me, hatun.
Will you serve me?
You raised me as a executioner.
You..
...sent me to kill my own parents.
your both mother and father.
Look at me, Poena.
I'm a victim too.
You are a victim...
I'm the victim!
-I'm the victim of your war!
-Never! Never!
You are my heart.
Only once... Listen to me only once!
Only once!
Look at the life Osman stole from me!
See what I went through!
Understand me!
Osman threw me into hell!
Do you really think...
...I'm the only evil one?
What about the life you stole from me?
Do you know what kind of hell you threw me into?
Why did you visit Osman and Bala then?
Sofia, tell me.
You're going to use me again, aren't you?
No, I don't want anything from you.
I don't want anything!
I couldn't make you happy, right?
Go then.
-You want me to go?
-Go.
Be happy with them.
But you should know this.
You won't be happy with them.
Because you don't know them yet.
You're going to give me
to them in return for what?
Sofia?
Nothing hard.
An alliance against Mongolians.
I offered Osman a helping hand to protect Bursa.
But it was very hard for me. Poena.
I ended the hostility for you.
Let's see if Osman will make the same sacrifice.
The demon called Claudius...
...slaughtered my alps in
front of the headquarter first.
He's also killed many innocent people of Beys...
...including children and women.
In this huge and vast world.
..I've seen many cruel and merciless acts.
I've seen Mongolians.
I've seen many others
coming from the east, but...
...I had never seen such a heartless enemy.
When I take off their heart with my teeth,
...I will see if they are heartless or not.
We will destroy both the
headquarter and the soldiers in it.
What about your child, Osman Bey?
What if attacking the headquarter
separates you from her permanently?
Did you think about that?
Sofia is a mad one. She'll do what she says.
The state..
...will never act without a plan.
Don't be worrying.
I planned every detail.
My child is my personal matter.
But the conquest of the headquarter...
...is for avenging the martyrs
and the welfare of the state.
It's what I say.
Tomorrow, we're going to
conquer the headquarter.
Koca Bey, Hasan Bey.
You'll go there at dark.
And infiltrate secretly.
When we stand against them tomorrow.
...you will push them from the back.
And we will take off their filthy souls.
Jij, no.
Jijig galnish...
Jijig gal...
Jijig galnish..
Brother.
Brother, I have tried many meals in this world!
I have tasted many meals...
Many meals but...
I have never eaten something like this.
I have never eaten something like this brother..
What is this? Where do they cook this?
It is the food of the Chechen
valiants of the Caucasus mountains.
Those valiants eat this meal
and fight against the cruel.
-Oh Praise be.
-Praise be!
Greetings to the valiants who know the
best food and walk on the right path.
Thank you.
Bless your hands and effort brother.
Thank you, Cerkutay Bey.
Brother, thanks to your hands and arms.
This jijig galnish was very delicious but...
...we cannot feel happy anymore.
So many caravans were raided.
People were killed with swords.
On one side this problem, on the other
side, the conflict between Shahzades.
There is no peace or order
left in the tribe, Cerkutay Bey.
Don't worry.
Are Muslims in trouble for the first time?
But if we stay united and together, we
will get through everything for sure.
For sure.
Besides, our Bey is with us.
-Thanks to Allah.
Even if I had a thousand
lives, I would give them all...
...to Osman Bey who
fights for the path of Islam.
His path is the path of The Righteous
Praise be brother.
He is a valiant.
Victories are won thanks
to courageous men like him.
Now let's eat our meal.
Tomorrow is the time for battle.
Come on. In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
A real battle is won by trusting
your brothers, Cerkutay Bey.
But you and Boran Bey parted ways.
Is that so?
Even if we are apart...
..our hearts are one.
And they beat with the love of war.
Also, we do not seek
separation on the battlefield.
Do not worry.
Now go..
Prepare well for tomorrow.
-Okay.
I cannot sleep. I will get
some fresh air if you allow me.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Can I come in, my son?
Come in, mother.
My son.
Mother...
My Alaeddin Ali..
The peace of my heart, the answer to my prayer.
You have already started preparing, huh?
You are in a hurry.
The sooner the better, mother.
Can't you think again, my son?
For our home, for me.
My beautiful mother.
My dear mother.
My decision is certain, mother.
Give me your pardon, mother.
You are leaving me helpless here.
Don't mother... Please don't do this.
I will come back.
I will serve my state with my
knowledge and my pen, God willing.
But..
I need to go now, mother.
The day you held that pen for the
first time, I prayed so much for you.
So that your knowledge would
become a light for your path.
Look, you are saying it, mother.
I am now walking on that prayer's path.
Please, mother.
I found out, my Ali.
Don't say anything, mother.
I don't want others to find out.
Especially not my father.
Don't. I do not want to put
this burden on his shoulders.
I came not to say goodbye to
you but to understand you, son.
But now, when my two
children are blind to each other...
Mother...
Mother.
There is such a fire in my heart that...
The fire keeps growing.
I am afraid of hurting everyone...
...if I run out of patience.
Leaving is the best thing now.
I thought I would come
together with my my daughter...
...but now I will long for
two more children, huh?
It will not be like that, mother, it will not.
You will come together with her, mother.
We will come together with our Halime.
But, I know...
My father will never leave her there.
Alaeddin... Alaeddin...
My son.
Come, my Halime.
He knows the infidels are
looking for a chance to attack.
But what is he going to
do? He is going to leave.
Our Alaeddin Bey will hold his pen...
Especially...
...especially when our state
is in such a difficult position.
Alaeddin.
He can go.
Let him open a new page for himself.
Maybe he won't leave if you talk to him, huh?
I said what I had to say to him, Holofira.
But Alaeddin..
Alaeddin already decided to let us down.
So his cause...
...and his brotherhood were not that strong.
Orhan.
Gonca told me something.
Did you really hit Alaeddin?
Did you tell him to return to madrasa?
Can I come in, my son?
Come in, mother.
My son.
Mother.
My Orhan.
Time passes so quickly, right?
It feels like yesterday.
You and Alaeddin would run and lie on my knees.
I used to tell you about the Messenger of Allah.
-Do you remember, my son? -Mother..
Do you think this situation does not hurt me?
I asked if you remember, Orhan.
I told you that..
...The Messenger of Allah
told his people that...
"The real warrior is the
one who defeats his anger."
Huh, my son?
I remember, mother.
You both were upset.
"How are we going to do that, mother?"
"'Anger is something we can't see...
...or cut with a sword. How do we defeat it?"
What did I say, my son?
Huh, my Orhan?
Mother..
"When anger blinds one of you...
...the other should be his eyes
so that in the end, you both win.
Don't let anger defeat you.
Never part your ways as brothers.
That's what I said, right?
Do you remember?
Why did you forget it when you
needed to remember the most, my son?
Huh, my Orhan?
He would be your eyes,
and you would be his eyes.
Why did you become blind?
I didn't want it to be like this either, mother.
But Alaeddin..
Alaeddin left me no choice.
So you had no choice but to hit him...
...and he had no choice but to leave, right?
What a shame...
What a shame that I
couldn't teach you anything.
The Kayi tribe is shaken by
Alaeddin's decision to leave.
These are Osman's good days, Vural.
Do you hear that?
Do you hear the sound of the doomsday?
It is coming for Osman.
What is your plan, Begum Hatun?
-When will Alaeddin set out?
-Tomorrow morning.
Good.
Let's throw this precious spark
into Kucar's hands and grow the fire.
Sofia.
What did you do?
Why did you attack the people?
I did what I thought was right.
The only harmless Turk is a
dead Turk. Why should they live?
I was even ready to sacrifice Poena to
make an alliance with Osman, but you...
I told you I didn't come here to
make an alliance with Osman.
I won't sit at the same table with Osman.
I don't want an eternal alliance with Osman!
When the time comes, we will kill him and
take our lands back. But now, for Bursa...
Enough!
You are talking just like a Turk.
Same words. Same thoughts.
It's like Osman is in front of me.
Sofia, understand this.
He thinks the same as you.
After he gets his daughter
back, they will draw their swords!
This alliance will bring
us death. Understand this!
We have no choice but to try, Claudius.
Otherwise, we will lose Bursa.
There is a solution. But this is not it!
Enough Claudius! Don't ruin my plans!
Get out of my way
Calm down.
Calm down. Calm down.
Now tell me.
How did Poena react to the alliance with Osman?
She doesn't know what to
do. She's stuck in the middle.
But she will do what I want.
You see?
No one is eager to make an alliance with Osman.
Now it's my turn. My move.
I invited Osman to the outpost.
I'll kill him there and
disgrace him at the frontiers.
There is no alliance.
I will never let you do that, Claudius.
I am sorry. I really am.
But unfortunately, you don't
have the power to do so.
No matter what comes between him and I...
...even your green eyes, even your red hair...
...you won't be able to stop me.
My Alaeddin, how can we leave like
this without saying goodbye to anyone?
My mother will get even more upset.
Leaving in the morning will
be even harder, my Gonca.
It's better to leave in silence
now. Come on, my rose.
Are you going to leave without
saying goodbye to me, brother?
My Fatma..
My angel...
What are you doing here, Fatma?
Why didn't you sleep?
How can I sleep tonight?
I knew you would leave quietly.
I waited for you.
-You can't go like this, brother.
-Fatma.
My angel.
I don't want to upset anyone.
Why are you doing this, brother?
Why?
We have more sorrow to deal with now.
Brother, don't go. Please don't.
-Fatma.
My pretty sister.
My precious sister.
I'm not going to foreign land.
I'm going to see our grandfather.
I promise you.
I will be back.
-Well...
Who knows when?
We will be far away from each other.
I will miss you.
We will miss you too.
A little patience.
Look at me.
Take care of mother and father, alright?
Look after them.
Sister.
Take care of my brother.
Don't worry, my bead-eyed.
I will take a great care of him.
Just don't be sorry.
But keep praying for us, alright?
Fatma.
My angel.
My precious.
Take care of yourself, alright?
Don't upset your brother.
Let's go, my dear. Come on.
Come on.
Here we go.
Father.
Hold this, sister.
May Allah protect you, father.
May Allah always help you.
Let's go, my dear. Come on!
Come on.
Have a safe journey, brother.
Messenger Kucar.
Orlok Kucar.
Orlok.
I was waiting for you, hatun.
Have a seat.
How did you know I would come?
Are they still following me?
Do you know what orlok means, hatun?
It means eagle.
The eagle is in the frontiers now.
And it is watching all of us.
Now tell me.
-Did you consider my offer?
-Your offer...
...is accepted.
Good.
I'll collaborate with you against Osman.
Sharpen your claws now.
I've got important news for you.
Shahzade Alaaddin...
...separated his way from his father's.
He abandoned the tribe.
I've heard that he's going to the light.
It is very important news, hatun.
Good.
One of Osman's children is in my clutches now.
Bring him to me immediately.
When you send his children to Olcaytu,
...will you spare Osman's life?
It's the price...
..of the khan's children.
Fight in the frontiers is inevitable.
Bursa and Kayi will be
the properties of Ilkhanids.
Your hands touch it but your heart is far away.
This silence of yours is
the greatest cry inside me.
I'm hearing your silent cry.
I see the fire in you, Bala.
You don't see, Osman.
You don't see the fire inside me.
My tongue is mute.
But my heart is lamenting.
I have neither a son beside me...
...nor words to say.
No.
Don't look at me like that.
It hurts me.
You think I'm going to the battle.
In fact, the hardest battle for me...
...is your eyes.
I'm right in the middle of the battle.
I can neither come back...
..nor go ahead.
Even if your tongue is mute,
you talk with everything else.
Your eyebrows and eyes are falling on me.
I can read your mind, Bala.
But today, what you say in
silence becomes a dagger...
...and hurts my heart.
Do I have permission my Bey father?
Come in, daughter.
Daughter.
Is Alaaddin leaving?
Mother.
My brother...
...left last night.
Your father left quietly and
you didn't tell me, Fatma?
Mother!
Bring my horse!
Kismet, prepare to ride.
We'll catch up with Alaaddin.
Not now.
She's too angry.
Alps!
What's wrong with you?
We're going to the battle!
Pull yourselves together!
Nobody will stand with their heads down!
My Beys! My alps!
Today is the day to destroy the devil's nest!
We're going to avenge our martyrs and ghazis.
Let's go.
Don't have a sullen face.
Since that day, I've been
thinking if there was another way.
My brother...
Orhan Bey.
Was Orhan Bey right?
There wasn't another way, Gonca.
While my alps were dying one by one.
...while they were burning alive
...if I hadn't drew back there,
...all of them would have died.
I wouldn't be able to with this guilt then.
You did the right thing.
You shouldn't think anymore.
This is a war.
You can win and lose.
With what you did, you prevented a disaster.
It wasn't a mistake.
You did the hardest thing.
You endured, Alaaddin.
Today, you taught me what endurance means.
Alaaddin, why are you removing the traces?
Who would follow us?
I learned endurance and
struggling from my mother.
She will come after us.
That's why I'm removing the traces.
-Let's go.
-Alright.
No! No traces at all.
He said he'd go to the dervish lodge.
Maybe he's gone somewhere else?
I couldn't see my son one last time.
My lady, when things
calm down, he will be back.
He won't stay there forever.
What we think won't happen
happens all the time, Kismet.
Alaaddin has gone.
I couldn't stop him.
I won't leave Halime, though.
What's in your mind, Bala Hatun?
I don't trust the snake called Sofia.
I'll go and take my daughter from Bursa.
We're going to Bursa!
Let's ride! Come on!
Who are you?
You...
You are me
You are Holofira.
You are me.
I'm not you.
You..
...aren't Holofira.
Then...
Who am I?
You'll find this out here.
Osman.
I was waiting for you.
Just like your sons did
...you will either run away or die.
It's up to you.
If you were clever.
...you would have let my sons kill you.
Soldiers!
Well..
Do you think I don't have a hidden punch?
Beys!
Allah is the greatest! Allah is the greatest!
Nice. An easy victory can't be a real victory.
Soldiers, attack!
Attack!
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Alaaddin.
Allah..
I felt happy that you are smiling.
But right then your smiles
get covered with sorrow.
I'm fine, my dear.
It's like, in my heart.
...I'm carrying what I left behind.
I can't forget them when I go away.
I know.
You're thinking about your father, huh?
Yes. Yes.
I disappointed him.
You say so?
Great Scholar Alaaddin Ali Bey...
...has become like a student
who has left home recently, huh?
What? Should we go back?
If you go back, I will do.
Hey.
This is the first day of our new life.
There is no going back.
Alright then.
If we're on the way, we have to go.
Trickster Hatun.
With a single word of mine.
...you start an indefinite journey.
Aren't you angry with me at all?
Alaaddin... Even if this way leads to a cliff...
...or embers...
...I will still walk with you.
You say so?
It means...
You love me so much, huh?
Alaaddin... Daisy...
You want a race again?
Fine.
Let's have a race and I will
give you a hard lesson. Scholar.
-You say so?
-Yes.
Let's do it.
So be it. Trickster Hatun.
-I will show you how to ride.
-You never can.
Let's see who rides faster.
Koca Bey!
It would be a shame for us not to kill
all of them for the innocents we lost.
Come, Claudius.
Now it's time to take revenge for our martyrs.
Come.
Orhan! Leave that dog to me.
Osman.
Stop!
Sofia.
By the order of the great
Emperor, I end this war.
Soldiers! Lower your swords!
Sofia, are you crazy?
Soldier! I am commanding you! Attack!
Stop!
I said stop!
What does the Emperor want?
He wants us to make an alliance
against the Mongols just like I do.
And in return...
...the outpost will be yours.
And during this time
...Claudius will be under your command.
Sofia, you must be crazy.
If you don't obey the order,
you will be punished with death.
Never!
I will never side with a Turk.
Infidel leader, we haven't
given up on taking your life either.
Soldiers, we are retreating.
Won't we go after them, my Bey?
Of course, we will.
I want them, dead or alive. Go.
Go, Koca Bey.
So, it's the Emperor's order.
If there is a game behind this...
The game is over, Osman Bey.
Now it's time for unity for Kayi and Bursa.
Hand over the outpost to Osman Bey.
So that you want peace...
...then you will do as I say.
My daughter Halime...
You will tell me where she is.
You will take me to her.
-Aykurt!
-My Bey.
Strengthen this outpost.
-As you order, my Bey.
If you tell me it's the Emperor's order...
...but play a game...
...I will slit your throat, not Mongols.
Alps! Come on!
You've slowed down. Scholar, huh?
Good, you must have learned.
Do you even leave a man
any mind to learn, woman?
I don't understand, Alaeddin.
I mean, when I'm with you, I lose my mind.
No, you can't make me forget
your defeat with these words.
I'll never forget it, Alaeddin.
Good, enjoy it for now.
You'll see if I'll lose to you again.
-So you lost on purpose, huh?
-Of course I did.
Someone's following us.
What? Who?
I don't know.
But they must've been
after us since we left the tribe.
I don't know what's waiting for us.
First, we'll find a way to get over them.
Come after me. Come on.
Let's go!
With our alliance, the Mongols will
face the curse of God, Osman Bey.
Mongols cannot be cursed, Hatun.
Anyone who sees the shine of their sword
knows that Mongols are the curse itself.
Everyone who once felt the Mongol
chains on their neck knows that...
...the mark left by Mongols
does not fade easily.
After the messenger whose hand I cut off...
...for trying to touch my
lands, are you saying this?
The Mongols that make the world unbearable
for you every time you cut off a hand.
The Mongols that rained their furor
on you every time you went too far.
From your alliance, I see that
Byzantium also seeks this dark fate.
Now listen to me carefully.
With this unity, with this alliance
my messengership ends here.
Orlok Kucar stands against you from now on.
Two little sparrows declared war on an eagle.
Pity. Such a pity.
The day you said you would annex Bursa...
...you started that war.
Two little sparrows, huh?
Two little sparrows.
Don't forget the birds of Ababil.
The Ababil birds that
brought down the elephants...
...also know how to cut the eagle's claws off.
If you want war, then let's fight!
Face me!
What a pity...
You chose to perish when you
could have been prisoners but alive.
Someone is coming. Get off.
Hide, come on.
Isn't that Meryem?
Meryem?
What is she doing with the soldiers?
Why is she wearing Byzantium clothes?
She is running away! Catch her!
Bala Hatun, what is
happening? I don't understand.
We'll learn.
Come on.
He does not deny that he came
to the frontiers for the annexation.
He says we started this war.
We did not start this war, but
we will end it, my Shahzade.
For sure.
I told you..
A decision other than the alliance would
mean welcoming the barbarian Mongol invasion.
Whoever threatens our state and nation
will certainly face the furor they deserve.
Why are you in a hurry,
soldier? What is happening?
Ma'am, Poena.
She ran away.
Poena.
Where did she go?
She is going south, ma'am.
-Let's go!
Are you playing games again?
What kind of a game is this?
Come on!
What will I tell them when I see them?
Meryem
Bala Hatun.
My daughter. You are alive, thanks to Allah.
Are you alright?
Did they hurt you?
Do not approach, Bala Hatun.
Meryem. Meryem stop. They
didn't do something bad to you, right?
I said stay away, Bala Hatun!
Come here! What are you doing?
Meryem, stop.
Stop.
I said stay away, Bala Hatun.
Stay away.
What are you doing here, my daughter?
Meryem what is happening?
I wronged you.
What do you mean?
Stay away!
What do you want from this little girl, huh?
Bala.
Osman.
Meryem.
What happened?
I...
...betrayed my family.
I betrayed you.
Poena.
Come here.
Halime.
You are Halime.
Halime?
My daughter...
Sister..
Osman.
My daughter...
Come here Poena.
Stay away.
Stay away!
Stop, my daughter. Alright.
No one will come close.
Stop.
No one approach her!
It's over, my daughter.
The nightmare is over.
Come.
Come, let's reunite...
I'd love to...
But I cannot come.
I made many mistakes.
I don't have the strength to look at your face.
No.
No, look. It was not your mistake.
It was my mistake.
I couldn't recognize my own child.
I couldn't recognize my own daughter.
Forgive me, my child.
Forgive me.
Come on. Come. Let's reunite now...
Come to your mother.
Come on!
My daughter...
Come on, the light of my eye...
My Halime...
I can't.
I can't, I shot you with an arrow...
How could someone ever shoot her own father?
Would she ever try to kill her mother?
I thought...
...you were my enemies for years.
This cannot be forgiven.
No.
-It's not possible.
-No.
Don't even say that.
Look...
Children make mistakes.
Fathers forgive....
Fathers always forgive them.
Huh?
My daughter...
Come on.
Come on, give me your hand.
Poena, don't do something stupid!
You did nothing wrong!
It was all my fault!
You did this! You did this!
You buried me in your own darkness!
You shut up!
Shut up, you snake!
Sister...
My sister.
Come, don't do this.
Don't make my mother..
..my father..
...don't make us suffer from this pain again.
Come.
My daughter...
My Halime...
It is not your fault.
You are the most innocent, the
purest among us, my daughter.
Don't do this to yourself.
Don't do this to us, come here.
Come to your mother.
Halime..
Meryem.
Poena.
Who am I?
I don't know.
What will happen now?
I lost my memories...
I lost my childhood!
My past...
...is filled with lies!
Forget about the past!
It's over now!
Look at me..
But now..
We have future.
We have a future together.
Halime.
My daughter.
Look at me.
There are five steps between us.
Do you know what five steps are?
This is our feast.
Today is the reunion day
My dear.
Come.
Come here, my baby gazelle.
Do you remember...
...what I told you in the cave?
What we did with that shadow play?
The wolf and the baby gazelle?
Do you remember?
I tired really hard.
But I couldn't.
I went to that cave...
...to kill you, father.
But it didn't happen.
It didn't happen.
Your heart didn't let your mind.
I don't know who I am.
Whoever you are.
Meryem or Poena or Halime
...you are who you are.
You are our daughter.
You are.
Right, Bala?
Yes. Yes.
We want you.
Just you.
I want to hug you.
I want to caress your hair,
my dear. Come to your mother.
Come.
You can kill me but don't do this. Come on.
Come here. Poena.
Look at me. I called you Halime.
I named you after my mother.
I never saw my mother.
But I wanted her to live with you.
I wanted her name to live in you.
My Halime.
My daughter...
Don't.
Don't. Look at me.
The past is over.
We have a future now.
Give me your hand.
Come on.
Sofia stabbed me in the back.
Are you surprised?
You once said she could do anything.
I expected anything but...
I never expected Sofia...
...to have an alliance with Osman
and go convince the emperor.
Demon.
One is demon. The other one is improvident.
Osman's killing Olcaytu's
daughter and grandson...
...opened the gates of Bursa for us.
Nobody can stop us now.
Neither Osman...
...nor your emperor who
believes in their alliance.
Damn the emperor.
As Olcaytu promised you,
..when all the heads falls on the ground.
...you will ascend the throne in Bursa.
Under the banner of Ilkhanids,
...your reign will begin.
But if we fail to take...
...what Olcaytu wants as the price of
his daughter and grandson from Osman
...then our heads will fall on the ground.
What do you want this time?
You vile dogs!
What are you up to this time?
Gonca, I know them.
They are hell hounds!
Just go away and save yourself.
I will leave you alone, Alaaddin.
Come here, dogs.
Come here, come here.
Gonca, be careful.
-Gonca?
-Alaaddin.
Don't be afraid.
You vile dogs.
-Come on.
-Come on!
Gonca. Gonca.
-Don't touch her!
-Alaaddin!
-Leave her! Don't touch her!
-Get off!
Leave her!
Alaaddin!
How long I looked for you!
How badly my heart hurt!
You saw it for yourself.
Now I've found you.
Don't do this, my dear.
You can kill me but don't do this.
I'm begging you. Come here.
Come hug me.
Come on, Halime. Come on, my dear.
Halime, hold our hands.
Halime, after you hold my hand
...we won't have sorrow but happiness.
Come on.
Come on, my dear. Hold my hand.
-Father.
-My daughter.
-Mother.
-My dear.
Forgive me.
Halime. Halime!
Poena.
-My dear.
-Forgive me.
-Don't Halime..
-No!
Halime!
-Sister! Halime!
-My daughter!
-Halime!
Halime!
My baby!
Sister!
My baby...